What business do you have with us?
We have no conflict with you.
We are only here...
To speak to the French.
Why are you here?
Why do you hate them?
When I was a child
I was taken captive by the French
I watched them boil my father.
And eat him.
From the royal Governor of Virginia:
Sir, the lands upon the Ohio River are notoriously known
to be the property of the Crown of Great Britain
that it is a matter of equal concern and surprise to hear that a body of
French forces are erecting fortresses within His Majesty's dominions.
His dominion?
Continue.
In the name of the King, my master, I have sent the bearer hereof,
Major George Washington, one of the Adjutants-General of this British Dominion.
We should have killed everyone of you.
Thou art not yet dead, my father.